i must make absolutely truth the reason why i chased them from uganda was because of the economy
of uganda uganda was going to be bankrupt that is the reason why i chased away the israelis
and you said you were friends with goldamer yes then you changed completely from an israeli
alliance to the arab alliance i changed from israeli alliance because israeli are criminals
and that they are not trusted people they don't tell the world the truth they were taken to
palestine as refugees and then they changed palestine to become a state of israel by force
of arms given to them by americans and the british that's why i am signing an executive order order
today to deal with bds so we can stop the madness that we should not invest in israel
that is why we're going to sign an executive order stating that our pension funds will invest
in israeli companies because we get a high return on our investment because they're doing the right
thing the challenge is with younger people more than 50 percent of young people in america get their news
from social media particularly tick tock that is where they were learning about what happened
on october 7th what happened in the you know days weeks and months uh to follow and so when you
think about how to tell israel's story and it's important it's not just looking internally it's looking
externally and particularly looking at young people because you know it's not just uh the usual suspects
it is a lot of young jewish americans who don't know the history and don't understand and so we are
living in a time of miracles and unprecedented opportunities and the challenge for us here
and with this all in because this is this is key the challenge for us here is to leverage israel's
successes into our successes and our victories here because we are one people israel's weakness is
ours and israel's strength is ours and now that israel has turned the entire geopolitical situation
on its head our job in the diaspora is to leverage those wins and win here due to our enemies here
what israel did to its enemies there and on that the iac is focused come on out be in community buy a
book and get it signed rsdp at amandaseals.com